myubam.com 2016-10-23

# PRIVACY POLICY | Usborne Books & More

#### **Privacy Statement Table Of Contents:**

  * Our Commitment To Privacy
  * The Information We Collect
  * How We Use Information
  * Registration and Contests
  * Cookies
  * Log Files
  * Our Commitment To Data Security
  * Special Offers
  * Choice/Opt-out
  * Notification of Changes
  * How To Contact Us

* * *

#### **Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. Educational Development Corporation, parent of Usborne Books & More, is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Educational Development Corporation collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

* * *

#### **The Information We Collect**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Usborne Books web site. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Name Address Email address Phone number Credit/Debit Card Information [Etc.] On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient’s address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: Name Address Phone Number [Etc.] 

* * *

#### **How We Use Information**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. You can register with our web site if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our web site will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our web site. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

* * *

#### **Registration & Contests**

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via registration or contests. Participation in registration or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest or to notify the winners and award prizes.

* * *

#### **Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to participate in any of our Sweepstakes, Contests or monthly Drawings that take place. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

* * *

#### **Log Files**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

* * *

#### **Our Commitment To Data Security**

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off- line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry – SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just ‘surfing’.

* * *

#### **Special Offers**

Guests will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter by email. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

* * *

#### **Choice/Opt-out**

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at [support@edcpub.com](mailto:support@edcpub.com).

* * *

#### **Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

* * *

#### **How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 800-475-4522 or send us an email at [privacy@edcpub.com](mailto:privacy@edcpub.com).
